Andy Bird is with us, the CEO of Pearson. Andy, welcome.
Thank you. It's great to be here. Great to see you in
person. I want to get into the share price reaction.
Citi has put out a note this morning saying results are
solid but lack a buyback.
That sizzle the market was looking for.
Why didn't you go with a buyback? You didn't do one last
year.
Why is there not one this year?
We just completed a £350 million share buyback last year.
We have a very healthy balance sheet. In short, we want to
maintain optionality. We want to see how the beginning of
this year plays out and give ourselves that optionality to
see how best to use the strength of our balance sheet going
forward.
What does it mean in practice? Are you saying you might
want to use the funds for an acquisition?
We made three acquisitions last year in Credly and Mondly
and more recently in our Pearson Vue business with PDRI. We
also want to be able to digest and integrate those
acquisitions into the broader group.
[Powered by Dubverse]